God Is Still Saying Something
During The SCOAN Live Sunday Service on January 3rd, 2016, Prophet T.B. Joshua revealed
the mind of God concerning Southern Africa.
These were his words.
First of all, Southern Africa, if I may talk to South Africa.
There will be a little rain at the wrong time which is not good for farming.
Many farmers will be discouraged.
That is Southern Africa.
When I say, "Southern Africa", the whole thing will shoot from South Africa.
In that vision, I was asking God, "What is the way out?
What can we do in Southern Africa, majorly in South Africa?"
The Lord showed me that the government should be encouraged by building dams.
They should be able to invest in dams and irrigation mechanisms,
using available water from the sea.
This will also affect power supply.
You will see the power supply becoming epileptic.
As time goes on, it will be very serious.
Epileptic means, it is today, it is not tomorrow.
It may be very serious.